<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
 * SysLog - A simple logging tool
 * Copyright (C) 2013-2020 Scott Warner <Tortel1210@gmail.com>
 * 
 * This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
 * modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License
 * as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2
 * of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
 * 
 * This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 * but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 * MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
 * GNU General Public License for more details.
 * 
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 * along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
 * Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301, USA.
-->
<resources>
    <!-- Exception writing the zip file -->
	<string name="exception_zip">An exception occurred while compressing the log files.
	    This could be caused by a lack of space, an error reading the log files, or even permission errors.
	    Please double-check your storage and try again.</string>

    <!-- No files to zip -->
    <string name="exception_zip_nofiles">There were no log files to zip. This could also be caused by not having 
        root access, or the commands to get the logs failed. If you ran SysLog with root access, please 
        submit a bug report.</string>

    <!-- Error creating folder -->
    <string name="exception_folder">There was an exception while trying to create the folder to save all the logs.
        Please double check that your storage has space and is properly mounted.</string>

    <!-- Error running the commands -->
    <string name="exception_commands">There was an error while running the commands to get the logs. If you did not use root,
        please restart the application and approve root access. Otherwise, please submit a bug report and include the SU implementation you use.</string>

    <!-- Unknown exception (Oh shit!) -->
    <string name="exception_unknown">There was an unknown exception while running. Please submit a bug report, and include the SU implementation you use.</string>

    <!-- No send intent available -->
    <string name="exception_send">There was no application available to send a zip file. The logs have been saved, but please install or enable
        an email application or cloud storage application to easily send the file.</string>
        
    <!-- Low space on primary storage -->
    <string name="exception_space">Your primary storage does not have enough free space. You currently have %.1f MB free. SysLog can try to free space by cleaning old log files.</string>
</resources>